<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Konr Larson - From novice to programmer</title><description>Thoughts, stories and ideas.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><generator>Ghost 0.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 02:10:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/author/konr-larson/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>History</title><description>&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Let me start by giving you a recap of my life. I was born in Iowa and moved around a lot but I always had my family and computers. When I was little my dad worked for many start up companies so I was named the resident cable rat, I would take cords and run them though the crawl spaces. After I would finish my dad would allow me to hang out in the office I always gravitated towards the IT desk watching the gentleman take apart computers. 

I started playing with computers shortly after I would take them apart and put them back together again. I would install a bunch software to modify and change to see how it changed. In high school I took computer programming and engineering classes so I could mess with all the tech. I was amazing. After graduating I attended college but it was not the environment for me. 

I moved back with my family and got a job as a computer tech. I started with just my basic knowledge but the man I worked for taught me a lot and also taught me some bad things and thats when I decided I wanted to be better then him. So I started my own company with a partner. I met wife during this time. It was great I did all the computer work so there was nothing that went out that I did not personal touch. It was a good feeling that I was helping all these people and providing a service for about half as much as anyone else in town. We were doing great and expanding quickly. I was good at it there was no problem I ran into that I could not fix. 

Then my partner did some questionable stuff and I gave im an ultimatum he then did it again and so I packed up all my stuff and left. I lost all my money I had invest so I then went to work for Home Depot to support myself, it was fun work I drove forklifts and loved helping customers. I was Team Depot coordinator, I handled all volunteer projects. 

I married the woman of my dreams and we had a beautiful baby boy. I switched jobs to go work for Lowes. But my beautiful wife told me to do what I love and that she would support me with whatever I decided to do. My cousin went through a accelerated software course call Hungry Academy, after that he was doing great. He suggested to me that I should look into attending Turing it was the new iteration of the program he did. They said that they could take someone with no programming experience and turn them into a developer. 

I then applied for the program, they had a intense process that included a resume, video submission, github letter, and lsat questions just to get an interview. I waited impatiently for a response. then received and email scheduling an interview. I was so ecstatic. I did my interview with and instructor from the school which was nerve-racking, I had done interviews but this could change my life then he had me do so lsat problems while he was watching and asking questions. I had no idea how it went but i couldn't wait for a response either way. 

They contacted me and told me I was accepted. I was a great day and a day that was so hard because I would have to move 4 states away and leave my wife and newborn son while I went to school for 7 months. As the day grew nearer that I would have to left it became harder to think I was leaving my family.I quit my job a week before I left for school to fit in as much family friends and fun. My wife and my sister took me to the airport and had one last meal with me before I flew off.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/welcome-to-from-novice-to-programmer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26f55fd2-3756-4f3f-997d-25fcdd59c71b</guid><dc:creator>Konr Larson</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 21:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welcome to From novice to programmer</title><description>&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Hello my name is Konr Larson. I am attending Turing school of software and design, specifying in ruby. I had little to no experience before attending Turing. It is going to be difficult but a very rewarding experience. This blog is going to be about me and my experience, and about anything else I find interesting.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/welcome-to-from-novice-to-programmer-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">532d8068-c324-4a33-96d4-1c85bd70a7c1</guid><dc:creator>Konr Larson</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>